I
Was worried people so crazy. Why are they so crazy? Why does it do so? Why does it have to say such things?
We're dying just outrageous
Guys you want to support the chat I still need a couple of memberships
Jimmy Rose. Yes, you got one. I don't know the other person that well
But congratulations to you too anyone wasn't joining membership. Go ahead, please. Hey, yeah, so yeah, summer's welcome
It's summer. It wasn't what you did. I don't think so
What that flirty diamonds was saying? They're saying horrible things. I mean they were saying you know disgusting
Alex, you know, I wanna
I know I had 41 people in the chat. Yeah, again again, but you know, you see what they're saying Jamie like
Pretty diamond. What are you doing? And then I can just see them wanting to oh
Yeah
Gonna see them say oh
It's a premium hold on all
YouTube no interruptions
Starting at seven in the month. This is a student. Hold on. Well, hey, they lower the price. Let's get it. I
Don't I hate the commercial the super commercial on YouTube anyway
Me, I don't know. I think I feel like I'm a YouTube partner. I should get free premium
There we go. I have premium
Okay
Hey guy, I got I got you should premium 14 bucks a month. Hey, oh hold on. Who's backstage Alex, huh?
And we're back take them home for our word Jesus
the
So
This guy that you're here
Right here
That guy's a riot. Oh, wow. I never heard you talk this much to gain your life
You're really animated right now
Just bomb just do
I
Think you're gonna have to come to the conclusion that's already diamond snake have to go permanently
Oh
Psyche listen to other people they're telling you
You should listen to what other people tell you to do you don't have to think for yourself you just tell other people
You just listen to other people
homebomber
Just do a good old man
Okay, hey
Bloody diamond another one
That's another dumb bitch
That says that word. Oh, he did this to me if flirty cared about you psych
She wouldn't have done what she just did you understand that
No, you don't obviously
Shot it was shocked. You guys absolutely shot. I'm so shocked
You don't go
Yeah, no, it makes sense
But it'll still bring the drama to it the views people come back the next day to see if maybe some obscene
Racist shit was said once again
you understand this I talk you want to what's wrong with obscene racism
it's a free country
So I country yeah, I just want to talk to me flirty dive a flirty dive and uh,
Oh, is it?
What's that? Sorry dive
Are you done crying? You were crying just a minute ago, Flirty Diamond.
What happened to your pink top? Did you switch clothes that quick and take your wig off?
You like things in your mouth, don't you?
I'm just being silly.
So that's that you bring a sick. Yeah, thank you
For them and left
Right
No, yeah, no, I know that's for never that the wig without the make-up. She's it's like something on a lollipop
Definitely likes things that are out. So yeah, she was like that thing
They I'm not gonna let you back on your you and 300 glow are from now on a package deal
I'm not letting either of you with any of them. So you guys leave when they don't want these
I'm gonna like I have you on let's turn each other's off
So you think it's very glow back that I'll move maybe leave back up. Maybe you lost diamonds some old several some old one
Yeah, Hannah says she took off her makeup and quick like a Superman. Yeah
I mean
It seems like happening
I want to have fun no more crying anybody on panel like one crying bitch of a night
We're not gonna we're not gonna be upset but tonight's gonna be a good night. I have a feeling
Where's who? Hold on. Where's my judge? She's I think she said she's off work
Pager you here
Page we're calling you to the carpet. Please come up
We're paging page. Hey guys
Here I'm gonna pin my baby page
Page we're paging page page here. Hey, LD. What's up LD Nick Johnson?
Guys who wants to donate a membership tonight? Let's put some more members in the chat. Wouldn't that be so cool?
Hold on. So I said, so hold on. We're gonna damage just joined Jamie's Cowboys this course. I'm very plugged in. Okay. So, Elsie
I say put a diamond just joined Jamie's Cowboys. Okay. So, Mater. Yeah, bud. How are you?
Elsie, how are you? Do you know Elsie?
Wait a minute. Is that I
I feel like I've heard that name before with some crazy stuff around it. Okay. Well, I'll do you I come up and defend yourself
What's up guys? No, no, no, no, I'm not getting oh, no, I don't I'm good
No, you don't want to get involved. Okay. Hades. What's up?
But I don't want to be around this big Johnson. How are you guys? I don't know. I don't understand it
I don't know Hades. What's up bud?
It's summer. You're right. Yeah. Okay. Wait. Yeah, it's summer. Maybe you very wise person, you know, if she is but maybe it's
I don't know. I just remember. I think I feel like I heard
That's why I think
Yeah, I don't know. We need to deploy we start sharing bonus for memberships. I just want to have fun
Okay
But also remember she's good guys
There's some here butthole you can get a membership and set it'll be I'll get the same enjoyment out of it. Okay, Bronzeberg
Ninja with a pencil birds. I owe us a burp
Bros. We're gonna come up
Yeah, sorry
This story is accusing me of some crazy things that she's saying I was saying some things that I would never say I would never say
I don't for by the way for the foot of the word crack or is not in my vocabulary the word
What else is she said? She said I said she she looked like Kim Joe's girlfriend. I didn't say that
I didn't think about it. She's weird. I think she didn't look like Kim at all. So yeah
She'd be like once I get in and then she kind of just goes off the deep end out of nowhere. I'm like what the fuck just happened
But she's funny
Summer with the short woman syndrome some is not short
Bronzeberg
I'm short
Stretchy was that a summer
We'll get to baby. Yeah, I'm only five feet
Yep, I little
But I got a big personality
Oh
What's happening? What's her name? There's baby. That's a baby. Hey, baby. Oh
I love baby
Yeah, do you like dogs summer you like dogs look
Yeah
My baby boy
All right, I'm gonna use the bathroom and stuff. I'll be back in a minute. Okay, so you are y'all hold the door down
Thank you. I'm in get it together
Thank you
How are you good? It looks like it's just me in you
Yeah, I think we're alone now
So if you had me loaded, were you gonna be alone in the room?
Yeah, Tiffany Tiffany's name. So if you and me were alone in the hotel room with a bottle of alcohol
We're just hey, yeah, so what would happen what happened after we drink the bottle?
Probably pass out
Passed out. Okay, so you passed out and you feel you wake up and you feel
There's like a tug a tugging on your on your nether russians and you find me there. What will you do?
Probably start slinging. I'm not gay
No offense. I got nothing against gay people, but you know
What do you say excuse me
Start swinging swinging. I I was gonna say we were room service and watch a movie I
Was I just touched your leg because I was trying to wake you up
You're the net you're another region like you're me
If we touch you you're gonna start speaking at me when I was gonna say let me order room service for us
LD
I see you back there. Why are you laughing next to each? What's so funny?
Violence you that's the first the first thing he goes to I mean, I was like, you know
It was like that was like a very playful thing. I was like, hey, let's just uh,
You know order room service and put on like you know
Terminator chew and like just hang out
And have if we drink a bottle and just have fun and he's like he's gonna start swinging at me if I touch if I just
Touch his knee to try to wake him up. I mean I
Doesn't mean he was like not sexual. I mean what my guys those minds were just only for botos in the chat
Though I know why no one it's like no, it's like there's zero likes like nobody
Nobody's don't even remember ships or like a dollar. Everyone's here on the panel. They say they're gonna beat me up
LD wants to beat me
No, he doesn't
No, he says he's saying he doesn't
What
What LD what when you and when you say nether regions the first thing my mind thinks of is the private area
Well, no, it means below the below the below the below the balls
Your toe your toe I
Understand if we're drinking you accidentally spill some fucking alcohol on my lap and you're you know mopping it up
You know, but I
Mean if I just
What what if I mopping up my tongue if I mop it up with my tongue
What is
I don't I don't think my girl would like that. I don't think my girl would like that. Uh-oh. Oh my god
Who's your girl your girlfriend now? Yeah, she's in she's in Long Beach, bro. I told you when did this happen? Oh
Man, she's all me. She doesn't buy me. Why is my girl?
the
No, it would be really awful now and stuff like that, but I think you'd be upset if you started
fucking around my nether regions
I said imagine
When you come I'm gonna I'm gonna take off my work clothes. It's got home. Oh my god
Oh, it's getting hot in here guys
Oh
Hey guys, he says it's a similar another region and then now he's half naked and now he's
Really very confused Ilya
No guys chip and deals whoo
You think you think I can get a job at chip and deals
Be like for you boy
Yeah
Geo, do you want to speedo?
Um
Not any more back when I was like on the slim team. Yeah
Did you see me in my American flag speedo dancing? I meant to your shower
That'd be cool for 4th of July. That'd be fun. Yeah, I know I wanted to I had to wash it up to wash all the stains
Yeah, I mean I got a little bit
Oh, yeah, how are you dickie?
Dickie likes you dickie be a fan big Johnson. This is city party backstage
I don't know. I don't think LG wants to show me the balls.
Oh, shit. I'm pretty bad at violating TOS.
Okay. He's not going to violate the TOS.
We have to go backstage.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
Pretty sure everyone's seen them already anyway.
Your balls are mine.
Mine okay
Are you're floating around on the internet too? I hope not
You don't find my balls over the internet. Please just give me a private message
So if I came out to if I came out to Long Beach, would you want to meet up?
Yeah, we're gonna do we're gonna hang out. Yeah, we go to a bar. Yeah, we go out for dinner
But what if I eat so drop what are you gonna what are you gonna order to drink? What are you gonna get from the bar?
Hey, I'm gonna get
Six from the beach when you get
What's a buttery nipples? I'm gonna get blow jobs
I'm gonna get that a drink a blow job. Yeah, what's in a blow job?
Has whipped cream. Well, guys, what's in a blow job?
No, it doesn't I know it has whipped cream in it and maybe it has to Lua
Make some lemon drops do some lemon drops. I like lemon drops lemon and lemon cello mood ranger Nick
Also, I've been wood ranger. I've won wood ranger love. I think I've almost I have my beer left though still
You ever have a long island ice day, yeah, those are good. Yeah, that's oh yeah, I have fucked up quick
LD I can draw a picture of you. I mean I have some pictures
I don't know if you know these people. Do you know TT Electra? I don't think so
You remember DJ like so. Oh, yeah. No, I remember. Yeah, I remember DJ electric. She's the one that's always on the
Avatar
You like yeah, that's a nice one. Yeah, okay. Did you know Gaudi?
God he's God. He's my God. Okay. You like God. Okay. This is God
Does he have both of his legs in that picture?
of the
Of course, I know JT. Oh, okay. So I have a question for you. So you were harassing a mentally disabled person and
You called him a hooker and then you had him fly to Florida
To meet somebody to humiliate him. I didn't I didn't I didn't make him fly to Florida. You called the hooker
You called the hooker. I called the hooker. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Okay. I just let you know. So here's JT. Let's see if you're there
Okay
He's a wolf man person. Oh, maybe you know, I don't think he has a beard
No, he's a wolf man. Are you crazy? Look man? You didn't see him on the screen. He looks just like that. Okay
You know jingle there's from his from his yeah
There's a single
Okay, I have
Where's my good?
I'm gonna write it next to you to set this scarlet. I
Don't know scarlet. You know, it's a you know time
H. Y. M. E. No, you know, um, you know, spunky
Yeah, I miss monkey. She's the she's the doctor the physicians. Yeah
No girls, you know, crystal ghosts, I don't think so, okay, you know, uh, Jamie's Cowboys
Okay, you know, J dog, J dog
No, you know, Dougie Doug
No, I know doggie dog. Yeah
Yeah, that looks like dog
You know
Exiled one
No, you got quite a lot of drawings over there. They're gonna money put money money for 20. I don't think so
You know how's the inner NYPD? I saw him on here. Yeah a couple times
But then with the COVID mask on
That's a that's a swat team. That's good. You know, you know
your Christine's dog posi I
Don't think so
Okay, so crucible goes once you got some real talent you've got some real time
Oh, yeah, your crystal ghost is don't give them so I have to show
Where are you?
Oh, here he is.
So, you know, that's who will go.
There's Arbiter. There you go.
That's who will goes.
Huh. Yeah.
You don't know him.
You don't know guys.
Now, you know, if you don't know, now you know.
Okay. So, you know what you guys know?
Who LD is?
Yeah.
And then Duke, yeah, Duke's in the background.
That's great.
and
You know have you seen
Have you seen jade jade jade he's cock
What you have a picture of jade he's cock I think it was I think he asked me to draw it. Okay, so anyway
How would you
I've been trying to tell psych here that fucking good luck with fucking trying to prod progress on YouTube this platform right here
You gotta bite your tongue everything you say you got motherfuckers in here trying to pour and bomb you like left and right
You know I mean I thought I gave you props because you fucking you actually fucking a listen bro
You should draw a picture for
I can joke. I mean, hey, a psych is just as kind of asleep before and I fucking I was like the last one on this fucking
Streamyard or whatever and I fucking you don't do it. I would never fucking do I don't give a fuck
I'm not a homophobe, bro. So what he's gay dude who gives a shit, right?
You know I'm saying LD Doug, you know me. Yeah, I mean it's cool
I don't I don't care that Amber sends him money to ban me or anything. I mean, whatever man. That's your hustle
I'm not gonna rag you for it
Duh
I mean, whatever
Hey, I do
What is your shirt, what is your hat say Chris Chris? Oh, I've ever I've ever dropped breakfast you want to see yours home
Look, I was trying to look I got a crowbar, right? I got a crowbar
This is I like you I'll do the crowbar. They're handsome. It's very good. I'll do the crowbar
It's like yeah, looks like a wanted poster
Listen I try my hardest
Wanted dead. I do the crowbar
Your hand it looks like I don't know you're holding there you're pulling. No, you're holding a
Listen the reason why because look I fucking I got batting stances. You want to see my batting stances
That's what we there. Yeah. Can you take off your pants?
Can you take off your pants?
Okay, well, you know, you know King Griffey Jr. Bro, like this is his batting stance right here
I want to see it in the jockstrap. Oh up high
I don't have a bat, dude.
I don't have a bat.
I'm bored.
But listen, everybody's talking about,
all these people talk about fucking,
I got these like on windows or doors,
I can get in, I can get in wherever I want with this.
Regardless.
That looks like playing from Eddie and Eddie.
Yeah.
How you doing?
What's up, LB, doc?
Good, man.
Just getting home from work, chilling.
Honk rock bro
Watching some toxic avenger
Hey, listen, what do you think about the elected this fucking? I mean, I don't know I don't know your religion. Well, you know you're Jewish
Without doing anything, I'm I'm in New York
New York elected a fucking and some wasn't that no no he hasn't been elected yet
He's won the Democratic nomination, but I don't think he's been elected yet
Yeah, I'm a Monty
It's not that he's a Muslim. It's they're not muslims. Oh, what is he a fucking he's Indian? What are they fucking?
Buddhist, I don't know but he's just a socialist man. He's fucking crazy and
The shit that he's saying about it's like fucking Cuomo that ain't cool
It's uh
It's gonna you know, New York has got enough problems, bro
I don't think so either I think I think he's way too young and way too inexperienced to be running New York
Like the mayor of New York is like almost more powerful than like the governor of New York
Right. Yeah, so I mean I
Was thinking about moving bro to New York shit, but fucking not it, you know fuck
I'm not cool. I mean, I'm you know, there's so much diversity in New York though. You know, I mean, there's every there's everybody
There's fucking there's everybody just like just like Vegas in a way. Yeah. Yeah, they're all
migrants
Okay, you guys go outside. What's up? I don't know you guys you guys having fun
What?
Hey, what I walk in your place chip poker or something. Why is LD this underwear?
I'm not I'm in my pants. I got pants on. Oh, okay
I mean listen, he's at his house. He's comfortable like that's what he wants to wear
And it's hot, you know, okay, yeah, that's what you have that put
To poor to afford air conditioning, no, I'm kidding, but
Well, yeah, you know, uh, you know where uh, uh
Yeah, of course, I live like an hour away. You've ever been there? Yeah, plenty of times. They got the nicest needle exchange
Let me tell you there's some real magic that happens under that boardwalk at night
With I know I heard about it, but there's like there's hardcore bands like hardcore bands from Jersey
50 on red that would be right
Fucking how's it go shit? It's fucking bad ass
I'm not a big hard core guy
There's a lot of hardcore punk bands like from the like like fucking the East Coast that are fucking that are badass. You'd like fucking
Ten yard fight dude fucking a fucking
Minor threat is from Washington, which is all
Yeah, I mean, I mean like I said like East Coast has got fucking they they got they got the folks you know there
Like I like the hardcore you know Jersey's known where I'm from in Jersey. We're known for ska. We got a lot of ska bands
Like we do like a lot of ska punk a lot of brass instruments and stuff like catch 22 and Street Light Manifesto and fucking
all those guys
Never really been in a ska
I love Scott.
A lot of punk bands hate, a lot of punk bands hate Scott.
Like this band, I learned that there's a song,
fuck the Scott, Scott's not punk.
What the fuck?
Take your fucking horse and shove him up your ass,
punk, not Scott, you know?
Yeah.
I mean, like a skank, skanking, is what they call it?
Little, that's fucking dumb, you know what I mean?
I mean,
Yeah, I mean, there's no there's no good pits, but I'm not a big hardcore guy like I like punk, but I'm not a big fan of like hardcore I
Think this seems dead though, but mostly the hardcore seems dead
You know DI
Yeah, dirty in the dirty. No, that's DRI dirty rotten imbeciles the eyes
I actually don't know what it means, but they're from the last band. I saw they're fucking the lead singer fucking Casey fucking
I see I see him twice
You know an MDC
You know you like MDC
Go ahead MDC. I
Know that I know I know I've seen I've heard it
They used to be called millions of dead cops millions of dead children. They changed their name so many times, but there
My ship rip. What's up? What happened?
What's up? Do my hello
I'm thinking isn't my internet what the fuck here dude. I'm tripping out what happened
What is up?
You guys want me listen am I still live or whatever because I thought my internet rip dude if I'm still here, dude, whatever. Oh
What the fuck did I say something crazy I didn't say shit
You know I mean like that's what I'm saying, bro like fucking YouTube is so hard to like progress on bro
You know what I mean if you're fucking if you're trying to progress
Oh you get a memory or some shit like fuck you don't get it
Yeah, I was talking about bands bro what's going on psych
Yeah, I don't know. We were just talking about bands. I wasn't trying to say anything.
But I mean, did you put me like, uh, am I still because I thought my internet ripped?
No, no, you're live. Yeah, you're live. You just put me backstage, maybe because I was talking
about the band M.D.C. What? It's a punk rock band. You can talk about bands on YouTube, dude. I mean,
listen, man. Yeah, I don't know, man. I don't make the rules. I just I try to follow them.
Like I said, I got banned on YouTube and shit.
I have this, I mean, I just come on here.
I'm on rumble, bro.
So, oh yeah.
I've never been on there.
Are you drinking tonight?
What are you drinking?
I just got beers.
Miller, high life.
PBR.
Hell yeah.
Miller to low life.
What was that 30 pack we got when fucking when I was at your pad and we went to the a that fucking the market
Corner store market deal after you fucking moved out, bro. I went back there dog. I got going there. I was chilling
Some fucking crackheads and like this hooker bitch and shit and I chill I didn't mean this guy that fucking red tarot cards
Actually right there by that spot. It's like the corner market
Oh, you're talking about the murder mark. You're talking about murder mark
Yeah, yeah murder mark up on 11th Street on Fremont. I
mean, it's hood. It's hood, but uh
Ever get the burgers they have pre-made burgers, bro
I never had that day. Yeah, they make food there and stuff
They got like a grill and shit like they got good food there, man
I used to go there all the time murder mark. It's like yeah
It's like there's like a cooler and you get like burgers
They're like a saran wrap, but then you could like microwave them, but I just ate it cold
That's a burger. She was fired. I was all drunk. Yeah
I just remember they always had that fucking big guy that was a cashier there and he would he has an Instagram channel where like
He just films like the crack heads outside the murder mart and like they're throwing up and like fucking like you know
dancing and shit and like
Just crazy shit that happens out there
Yeah, that uh, the people that work there you have to be fucking hard like those fools they've run that you know
That work there fucking are fucking they don't play games like
My friend my friend Abe just got sworn in as a firefighter in Vegas today
Nice hell yeah, yeah, you got through the Academy and now he's a firefighter in Vegas today
I would love to be a firefighter dude firefighters are the coolest people bro like firefighters paramedics
So I always I should chill a paramedics back in the Navy like they're fucking they can drink me under the table
Like I'm a nurse. I'm a nurse
Yeah
Yeah, I'm living, you know, I got felonies on my record, so I'm limited on like my what the shit I can do and shit
But yeah, I feel you
Dude, my my roommate's boyfriend just went to jail for a year. He's doing a 345 or something whatever 364
Like a year in County
Yeah, like a year in County
So basically that means like
in the county jail, he's gonna be like an AMA worker.
Like he's gonna be like a trustee.
That's what he fucking, when you get that sentence,
you're gonna be hooked up.
Like you're not gonna be like a regular general population,
but you're gonna be like a blue
and you're gonna like, you're gonna help the cops.
That's fucking deputies like fucking like do the work,
like mop the floors.
Yeah, 365.
I mean, that's what you're gonna be.
Fuck that guy.
Oh, I'm sure it's better than prison, yeah.
Yeah, dude, what are they gonna say? I always see I always see your sister in in chat Jen
Where in here?
Not in here like on good times, you know good times is original his main channel got banned
No, I haven't talked to good times in like two years
Well, Jen goes to his channel like fucking a lot
Yeah, I don't I don't go over there
What was I gonna say
Yeah, there's this one chick bro, I need to fucking I'm trying to get like trying to get with her
She works at uh, I don't want to I don't want to leak where she works
But she works out here at this restaurant like 24 our restaurant. I hear baby
And I always come in with like fucking yeah, I think tool the band tool. I got multiple tool shirts
Yeah, I love dude. I love Maynard. Yeah to awesome
Yeah, she's like that's my favorite band. Oh shit. I was like, hey, well, you know, you got Instagram
Let me hit you up you like you go to shows. I'm I want to like invite her to a show with me and try to
See what's up take her take her to huntridge tavern, bro
Yeah, I mean where I mean wherever my favorite my favorite bar
I mean besides evil pie on Fremont was always odd fellows odd fellows was fucking cool
Dude, I've seen I've seen so many bands like so many public that the pump scene out here in Vegas is way bigger than fucking
San Bernardino, I guess say that from wherever, you know me
Oh, yeah, but yeah, I like tonight, you know double down saloon. You ever heard of that? Of course
Yeah, of course, it's right by paradise and fucking whatever they have some crazy shit going on tonight
I was gonna walk there. I'm like two miles away. That's right by Batista's the hole in the wall
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a yeah, but uh, I
Don't live at the same spot. You remember you I move bro. I live in the hood
I live by Twain and University Parkway. I remember my ex man
We used to go to this bar on a was it Sahara it was either Sahara or like spring Mountain
I think it was maybe spring Mountain, but the Phoenix. It's like a gay bar, but man
It was fun like they play good music you could dance there like the fun time like Phoenix was cool
Where a golden Tiki golden Tiki was good
Yeah, that's legendary golden Tiki's legendary. But yeah, uh, you want your girl to the gay bar?
Yeah, the Phoenix. Yes, I mean that girl. I do. I'm flying her out from Long Beach. She's living in Long Beach
I'm trying to convince her to move out to Jersey with me and like restart shit like
So she's flying out here soon, I'm gonna try to convince her like yo like it's changed I got my shit together
I'm not a piece of shit anymore
I mean Long Beach fucking I did all of Southern California is like expensive. I wish I want to move right near the beach
Yeah, dude. She lives in like Long Beach like you tell me how expensive it is now
She fucking hates it how expensive it is. I'm like come in Jersey, man. Like I'll take care of you like it's fucking
Start a life again in Jersey
Do it up man. Hell yeah, yeah, she's gonna come out and chill or whatever it's when aren't you a piece of shit?
Don't know Hannah since you started growing hair on your nuts
How was LD a piece of shit fuck you bitch I
Never been a piece of shit. I mean I was a piece of shit to her
Okay, okay guys, we're making fun of him now no
Why why what do you think Alex what's going on here?
These guys doing Alex what the hell up an LD and the other in the fat book you want to back up
Of course, I do I came here to talk to them
You're talking to them nicely and
Yeah, I wanted to tell them something really important. Okay
Wait, so I came up and you dropped them. No, no, no my friend LD
You're not getting right you say you have a girlfriend
You don't seem gay. You're not gay. I don't know what I said, bro. I'm sorry
You're not gay either, right? You said you're trying to get with some girl at a bar
You know some bullshit for none of your gay. Check this out. Psyche is gay. You know what he said yesterday, bro
I don't care that gay people do get ready buckle up door to see cuz Kansas is going bye-bye
There's a thing called docking docking like a ship docking like think of the word docking
So he said that he puts his little his pee pee against his tip against another dick
tip
Of an on circumcised man, and then they pulled the skin the foreskin over both
What's happening man? You okay? Yeah, you okay? Where are you from? I've met you before. I think I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. Oh you've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's panel. I've been on Pete Akihi's
Are you Reggie Demons dad? Are you Reggie Demons father? Are you?
No, no.
No, okay.
No, no. You have a chance to smile.
I might sound a bit like him, but I know who he is, but yeah.
I'm going to fix him. I'm going to fix him. I'm going to fix him. I'm going to fix him.
I'm going to fix him. I'm going to fix him.
But they see me
Is that really gotty is that gotty? Yeah
Go to is that gotty is that you got to I don't know if it was he's a cutie. He's a cutie pie. He's in a wheelchair
Yeah, buddy is really good with the wheels were the bad day
I don't understand
Buddy where you go?
I don't know if it's the weed, if it's what's happening, it's not really going to be Ellen.
Don't you never turn this camera on, man. You never turn this camera on.
Yeah, LZ is, LZ is, she's eating that red light, oh my god, oh my god, I love it.
Come back in the red light, come on.
I want to see you in the red light, red light.
Rock, Sam, you don't got to put on the red light.
Exactly, exactly, you remember mine. So Chris K, are you okay? Hey, I think I asked this here,
so you're telling me I'm being a channel, but it must have been months ago because I'll be,
you look like Regents even, it's like father or something.
are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are
It's not Raging Team and I'm not him, but Raging Team is a white dude man, he's a white
dude man.
He's white, he's white.
I don't know what the hell are you, you're a little bit white, he's a white boy.
I'm off. I'm off. I'm off. I'm
Like what's up? I'm circumcised like is that you got you guys a you know
What you want to have you'd like circumcised
What's up
I don't have fucking you know was it this the the access my shit's cut like I know when I was a baby
Yeah, I mean why are they all men on your panel talking about circumcision and stuff and cocks and all that and this guy here
He's got this guy. Yeah, he looks like he's come straight out of the blue oyster bar
I mean, what's what's going on here? Like what kind of stream are you running, bro?
He's got his chop off he's showing his boots and he's got this weird shit going on he's gay moustache
This other guy to my right is talking about circumcised cop
I mean what's happening there? What kind of game? That's the Blue Waste Bar Mustache. What is happening here, man?
I don't know. Maybe change the stream title to that. This is the game show. Welcome to the Blue Waste Bar.
Let's get some beer. Let's get some beer.
As is it. So tell me about your first gig experience.
I know you had one. You had this one. What happened? I want to hear it.
What happened? I got kidnapped in a van. They pinched my tongue. Look.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
me, or LV, but there's no gay experience, I'm here to,
I mean, I fucking I used to like a live stream like IRL like walk around. I've been to live in the gay bars out here in Vegas
Did you visit a warrior hold?
One lawyer hold no
Can we see the
Other people that are like our gay or whatever. It's okay. It's okay. Chris
You have to be a judge, you have to be a judge, go ahead, go ahead, you have to be a judge, you have to be a judge, you have to be a judge, you have to be a judge
Can we see the power of that, you've got the...
I wanted to see your tattoo man, that you've got a Peter Pity's BKG, Bica Pity's gang, and you've got a tattoo on that man
That's the key is one nice man. I think that's great. I love that. That's that's called respect. Like, you know, you've got respect for that lady.
That's great. You know, I'm not a homophobe or whatever dude. So I can, I can, you know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
I don't know. So, as I said, go ahead, guys. You talk. You guys are getting so long.
I mean, I've talked to other, like, people that are, like, you know, gay that,
fucking, they're like, they like the foreskin or whatever. I think I'd like,
I think I'd like being circumcised. I'd like, I'd like not there, like, fucking, you know what I mean?
That makes sense. Yeah, me too.
You're circumcised, too.
I don't want to talk about it. I don't care. I don't care about sergums. I don't care if you're cut or I'm cut.
Is it an ant either or?
I thought you wanted it. I thought you wanted to hear about our first gay experience.
I don't want to hear about it anymore. No, I'm pretty straight.
I'm disgusted. I'm like, oh, this is what gay things are about. I don't want to be part of it.
I'm sorry, you guys are pretty straight because now I'm disgusted with men.
Okay, guys, how are you doing?
Guys, what do you think, guys?
This is too much. I mean do you man do you and live your own life? We're all fucking whatever makes you happy man. I don't care
Zach I'm not I'm not here to judge you or the way you live
Obviously what you guys obviously want to fuck each other so I was
Now bro me and Chris K have met up in real life like a couple a bunch of times we used to live in Vegas together like
If we wanted to fucking show we would have when we were meeting up like that should never happen like no one
But yeah, you know I mean like fucking uh, I like you know like pussy dude, so
You know LD listen LD's just got he's got that he's like he's like no, he knows punk punk rock. I like
We a we came up with granola bar
We came up with granola bars, you know, yeah, don't get into it, but you know, you know, I'm talking about right now really I
Want to know how we got you look at a beautiful girl about granola bars
Have you ever seen a beautiful girl in front of you and you just like oh my god
That's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen in my life and then your brain says no
I want Harry Dick in my mouth and someone explained to me how that works
I can't as my mind doesn't work that way. That's scary
Oh, yeah, cuz you're not gay I'm trying to get a gig out here Chris. Can you explain it?
Here's the thing could I say this real quick like I mean I've seen like especially you look there's the on internet
There's there's trannies
Are you by Sack to
No, I'm just saying bro. I've just I've seen there's trainees out there that I'm just like is that he's hard to tell
You know, I mean, it's like is that a like well, that's hot shit. Wait, that's a trainee. Oh fuck
You know me that's now if you're a man that will never happen
Unless it's like the trainee of the century
Like you know, you might vote for it if it if they went that full of the chat and did this
But you know that your man reader will always go off
Like that's not there's something off there. You'll see something a jawline
Anatoms apple die something will go on the main radar, bro
Right come on. Lay down dude. Lay down
All the cities like sometimes it's hard to tell you some of these fucking trannies out there fucking. It's like, you know
They got fucking guys titties. I work. I work
I work with a tranny and I got in trouble because I told her have a good day, bro
to
Walkin into work. She was walking out of work. I was like, yo man. See you later
Have a good day, bro, and she like fucking went and complained about my god. Yeah, and you okay's that crazy
He's super that shit. Yeah, that's how crazy the laws are here, man
That's funny
You're like you can't call me a bro. I'm like
Me get the fuck out of my face. You're a good lawyer. He'll sue or she will sue that as for something so I'm crazy
When I woke up this morning, I was in America and last time I checked I got freedom of speech
I could say whatever the fuck I want
correct
But it's getting more limited and limited by the day
You know and lawyers are insane
I got to give you I identified a girl. He violated my rights. He called me bro
It could be that simple, you know, if not a lawyer with your money your rights are in impeding on my right
Exactly, I have the right to say whatever the fuck I want and if it offends you will go fuck off
There you all right
That's the American way
Yeah, well I was raised
But in 2025, it's the opposite. It seems
Like you can't say that to me. I can I'll take it or do you breach my fucking civil rights?
I used to fucking ice play baseball and like literally all the way up to fucking a varsity fucking
That's the best I could play job baseball literally
I wish I would have focused on every team that every team that I was on bro got first place
All the time every every team out all the way in the money
Those weren't first place trophies. Those were participation trophies
No, they were first place. I actually got first place. Do you like fucking?
What position yeah, that was my next question. What position?
Third base and center field because I could throw I could throw fucking I could throw from center field
I could throw on the home plate
I fuck have an arm and I'm fat and I'm fucking from third base and get the first quick
to raise the screen and
Center field and center field
Fucking uh, yeah, you know, uh, I was oh, I pitched back when I was in the month
I I was wild I used to beam people in shit
And all the teams that we were playing back in the day
They're like this guy like he's like too old to be bitching like everybody was scared
But my birthday landed my birthday landed on some day where I was like I barely got in or whatever and I fucking uh
So my best memory so my life was literally man
I made it the second place. So I that's why I want to say no when you're like first place because actually we got into like the
World series of the literally cheap and we took second
But still that's not my life
Yeah, I got we got first and then we my team went on well not my team
But like it was like varsity fucking up like high school. No
He's this fool fucking listen, bro. You ever you ever play, you know, you play baseball, right? Oh, we got sick
thumbs up
it's fun
you guys wanna see
the
no hey listen
don't add
just show it
hey where you been sick
fucking buster
he's been getting ready for bomb bomb psych again
that's what he's been
he's prepping
Over here. Okay. What are you doing, bro? Like listen get your shit together, bro
You're over here streaming some fucking bullshit. I see you like but you're not even there you're afk half the time
I was jealous. He's jealous. He's a little feeling
That's like he's flying right by him. He's jealous. He's got to take him down
Nobody wants like that's why are you confused like when you stream every every time every every
Second you're streaming like provide content. Don't fucking stream just AFK shit, dude
I'd like leave your monitor on with some fucking
Bullshit like some Beatles fucking like fucking in the desert like oh Beatles
That's crazy
That's the funniest I love when that happens it's on activity. It's no party
I'm just giving you a heads up bro like it ain't gonna get you more viewers do people are gonna think that's what you do
Normally on your stream, so you gotta when you stream you gotta be
I'm just impressed. He has a shirt on he's always show this and his beard looks like a chest hair. It's a mystery
There's bats going on
I'm just saying
Well, he's happy tonight for some reason. I think he took mushrooms cuz he usually just hold on
Never been and I never will be intimidated by police. All right, let's be clear both
What?
Hey, can I shift yours to you?
What if I give it?
I don't know.
I'm going to please you.
He's a girl.
He's got a girl.
Only a girl would put that smile on his face.
so tell us about it today
did you get a girlfriend?
you're going on a date?
because you're glowing
you got some cookies
that's exactly what
a police officer
would believe
that's exactly what a police officer
would think
Hi, come on. Hi. Hi. Join the panel. Okay. Everyone. I'll be telling me to
This is a rare occasion
He's pregnant. He's blowing like a pregnant woman. You scared me
He likes it. I mean, he likes it. He likes it.
Alice and I are happy for you guys. Chris K.
I think he's going to be the, he wants to be like the tarot reader at the wedding.
I don't know if he gives us, I think he's a good reader.
Pie, Pie wants to help us say hi. I think Pie says he wasn't.
Do you know Pie, Chris K., or no?
What's up?
You know Pi?
Oh, Pi Rana.
Pi Rana?
Who knows?
Everybody say Pi.
What about him?
Well, we want to come up on panel and say hi in just one minute, two minutes.
She's here?
Yeah, she's in the chat.
My hot sexy Pi with the curly black hair.
She said, Chris is interested.
Okay, Pi, Chris is going to give you a reading if you want.
Oh, she's got a crush on you.
Chris, me?
I would never say that.
Can you tell
Tell page. I said what oh, I want to like I want to like talk to people no pages my natural
Hi yours read the room. Well, come on. Bye
Oh, hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
I think she's DJ Electro. It's one of my theories. No, she's not
We're gonna settle this one's the problem and DJ Electro will play will come on the panel
Hi, DJ Electro hold two pounds
You got 40 ounces of malt liquor Mickey's out there fireball I know but you got 40s of Mickey's
I have a drink of Mickey's since I became old enough to drink
Do you think you can drink a 40 of Mickey's in under 10 minutes?
Probably, yeah
A 40? I can drink a 40 in under 2 minutes
Yeah, it was fun
the
that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that that
You know all you got to do to your wife. I used to be it you guys want to
It's you in the 40s you're doing 40s. I was like I was like 16 years old
I drink 40s my mom was like hey, you know what she's like try a wine
Crazy or say nice
One saying that's for you would fuck you up
It was
See
Look at that
Something bro say say leave the shows to say I
See if anything happens to me, I'm gonna leave the show to say you could have my show. Okay, say, okay
I bet he happens to me. What's up my name?
Do you like me are your friends now?
He's in love. He's in love. He's one nipple
Who is it?
I never had a problem with you psyche. I told you I
Told you bro. I never had a problem with you. I
Tried up psyche. I try to put you on to shit, bro. I try to put you on
bro
I
Call me a hater, bro. You want to call me a hater, but I put you
If you want anybody kicks off you can tell me let me kick up people I look your appearance
You know you have just people on the panel anybody want to kick off or are you cool with everybody here?
I
Enjoy the power of censorship that you have
Chris is very fun to be up now with game you read it
Yes
He's like
Are you mad at me forever?
You know, I just see what it is. It's okay
Wait, baby. What is it? Can you still love me even no matter what you see it is we sweet friends?
They you're mad at me forever. I don't want to be mad. I don't just be managed
I'm not mad at you. I like I'm like, oh, that's my pie like I never was mad at you
I've never met you you have mad at me for some dumb reason
Yeah, it's just hard for you to listen like you're I know you're somewhere else like what's the point. Okay.
No, she's right, bro. You need to be grounded. Tell him, Rana. Tell him. Like, how do I talk to someone that like anything I say to it doesn't like hold. Exactly.
Tell him he'll listen to you. I've been trying it goes in one ear, not the other
Rana, I think you're the only one that can save him. Honestly
I swear, I swear
You're the only one like you're like
You were with him from day one like you were born together like they're not holding hands like you're the only one
Shut up all these people like I was there from day one. Oh, that's your shadow
It's been hell. I don't mean to fucking watch this shit, but we're all we all fucking rock a holocaust here
So you better fucking get grab a bottle get something get drink with us. If not, oh
I'm first of all, that's peer pressure and I don't appreciate it. You know
Oh these white glasses
Bring me back to one of the crazy days of my life
I was in this um
I had to like being this part
What do you got what do you got pie?
Where'd he go? I love Alex
No, the white glasses on my favorite because one day I almost died and then I was in a parking lot
And I just stayed there for 16 hours straight. It was super sunny and this never happened to me in my life
The sun was so bright and start reflecting that my eyes were like water like after like
Like six hours and just started fucking with my eyes. I'm like, yo, what the fuck?
like I can't like it was too bright there was no shade nothing and I don't know where
I find these sunglasses like on this like a rock thing just out of nowhere and it was exactly
what LD's wearing they were white shades like that and I just like what the fuck and I picked
them up and I put them on they were a little small for me but I wore them for another 14 hours and
doing outside in the sun for six hours that's crazy what's up I don't I'm glad
to hear that rolling up oh yeah it's not my it's not my what like is it like a
This whole thing feels vegan. It's weird, but okay, it feels that's how much it papers were vegan
Yeah, but like no
It feels like a thing of cardboard the glue definitely has animal products
Strange you have what what what strange
Think this is the chocolate one chocolate you don't care you go by weed you don't fucking like ask for what like what you
But after I totally forget I don't care anymore. How many grams is yeah, I always get like you know, sativa doll
Three and a half what of weed buds three and a half what?
Of this three and a half what unit of measurement. Oh, you can't see oh grams
Okay, yes
Hey Alex
You're lucky fucking psyche even lets you on this shit without you're not even counted up bro take off
That's true. Alex. Why do you hide you have a good identity yet to protect?
Yeah, he's a cop he's undercover
Okay, that's okay
we'll protect you
thank you thank you
like I said this ain't my shit but you know what I mean fuck it you don't even run cam bro
like your fucking opinion get the fuck out of here
Chris your camera is like about
128 by 128 pixels
so what
As you can see me, right? You know, I mean, at least I'm not fucking over some fucking really
It's like a security camera footage
Where you look at it and you're trying to determine the person's identity, but you can
What are you talking about?
Like my shit is clear. You can see my face very. I know I can see
You can see all of the wrinkles and all of the
What's it called? Yes, not wrinkles
the
Valleys and peaks of my face
You can see mine, too. You want me to see my dick there's reality
I bet that my dick is smaller than yours
I mean Chris K. Chris K. I'll bet money
Chris K. I'll bet money that my dick is smaller than yours. How much money you want to bet?
Chris how much money you want to bet that my dick is smaller than yours
How much money you want to bet? I'll put money I'll put a lot of money. I'll put money down
I'll put money down right now stop paying to see dick
Hey, hey sick, are you circumcised?
Hey, you guys are just teasing Sino
That's crazy
Yo, are you circumcised is a crazy question
Yo, Pyron, are you circumcised? No, I'm not from sovietia. I am I'm proud to be circumcised bro
I was circumcised when I was a little baby in a Catholic church
I'll just be honest, bro, like, I, you know,
I just never thought.
Your parents, your parents were so sure
that you weren't gonna shower when you were older.
They're like, let's cut his dick now.
What the fuck?
I mean, let's be honest though,
uncircumcised dicks look fucking weird.
What do you mean they look weird?
They look weird.
That's compared to what?
Circum-sized?
Like, it's the same kind of weird, relax.
When you-
Wait, so I'm sorry.
Why do you-
That's why you draw a wrap.
You draw a peanut.
When you draw a penis on a sheet of paper,
do you draw a fucking circum-sized dick
or an uncircum-sized dick?
That's true.
That's very true.
Hey, Pye, what's your first one?
Would you rather-
Yeah, but no, here comes size six.
You can just pull it.
And it looks like circumcised anyway, so you know what Rick relax you you think too much about this
So you'd rather you'd rather have a certain on circumcised I
Rather the guy not been
Utilated in her but you can't change anything if it happened to when they were kids
You know all I'm gonna say I'm gonna say is that you're you're trying to say that male
Circumcision is not the same thing
And and I don't think that's fair just because it's common just because it's common practice doesn't make it any less
Like awful real. It's true. They had no other choice back then. They didn't have access to clean water
poor guys
They didn't have access to clean water back in the day
No, like you couldn't bathe so people getting guys are getting a lot of infections
So it helped but now that you can shower daily. You don't need circumcisions anymore
Jesus
Yeah, yeah
I'm gonna get done based on talking about circumcision. Yeah. Yeah. Are we done one with the torture?
Alright piranha, welcome back
You've been talking about circumcision since you came back
I'm gonna suck on a tits
like you anymore you gotta go cleavage baby what are we doing your hair is hot in your
cheeks I bet this guy and your whole face acting turned me on
she's hot man you know how she does it to me you know how everybody has to look in
a thing like I brought her clothes, I bet this guy would pull me the fuck on
bitches that he had arrested I bet she does it for me man
He's got a she's got like two kids, right?
I don't have any kids oh my god don't say that.
You hate kids?
Nobody believes that.
I love tight pussy.
No, no, no.
I love it.
Nobody believes that.
You miss it.
You miss ready baby.
You.
When you said I have no kids. I was like, oh my god, no kids came out of that
You know how tight that pussy is and you know, I love this girl. He's so hot
So that's just a mantis baby
Loose as a granny definitely
No, not tight at all. I think you're lying. I think you have at least one kid, right? No, I don't have anything
I live at home with my parents still. I don't have kids.
Wait, how old are you?
I'm 40. Like, I just turned.
And you live with your parents?
Yeah, I'm not doing too good right now. But I'm working on it, so, you know.
You're like, damn it.
First K is holding back a rant that he would give to anybody else if it wasn't you
You know, I'm on Sykes YouTube and shit. I don't want to fucking you know, I got respect for fucking
No, you don't Chris
I
Don't care I don't care people you get everybody fucking says you know gay this guy like I don't give a fuck
He still is my homie dog. I feel like he's my friend
So fucking I wouldn't you know, I'm not you know
I wish him the best if he's trying to progress on YouTube this platform YouTube is the hardest one to fucking do because it's
Sensored it's censored. You know what I mean? So fucking you gotta you gotta be careful what you say
Type shit, you know, I mean, so that's that's I mean, that's real
Chris K. Just enjoys participate participating in
diplomacy and and the politics
That's fine, that's fine. I feel like Chris I feel like Chris literally like
He got like he got reprogrammed by all the prison politics and shit
That like literally like it's so it's so weird you think about it, right?
These guys right in prison that they they become obsessed
They're like almost autistic with the rule following and like they have their own rulebook
They have their own code of conduct
That's how you interpret it.
And so what I'm saying is you would think that if somebody was so keen on following
a rule book, if somebody was so keen on following a set of rules of code of conduct, isn't that
the same thing as regular law?
You could just follow the regular laws that are for everybody else you could follow the same code of conduct for everybody else
But people become institutionalized
People become institutionalized. It's crazy
Hey, sick by the way, I got listen I didn't mean to
Remember I was down in GTA last time a couple days ago member that shit
right
I fucking I got it, dude. What happened was my fucking shit ripped my phone died
It might actually die again guys by the way, so my rip off try to come back and
Long story, but yeah, I got it dude. So
Are you still live
Especially psych
When I was talking to a page. I didn't mean to like leave my shit my internet ripped like a diet
It went off and I was like oh fuck now
So they yeah, I just went to sleep
But yeah, I was so mad Rick Hellcat mad Rick
You know
You're okay. You should join this stream dude. I know it like
Okay, doesn't usually join streams, but
Look at school
Doesn't he have his own that's like he focuses on
Yeah, I mean, I don't know you would only know that if you watch the streams I
Watch a little bit you would insist that you don't
As you just I have I used to watch you guys all the time. Are you to be subscribed to Chris? I
Know on YouTube right I got banned but yeah, hellcat fucking it is what it is, but I'm not you know
I'm almost to my five-hour premium fucking
I'm not gonna like stop it
I'm just going to keep it going until I get it.
Well, no, on Rumble, like on Rumble, as a creator,
you have to get a specific amount of hours streamed,
like on specific, like,
You know tight like titles like fucking 30 hours over here five hours over here, and I'm getting my shit done right now
That shit so I know
I've been thinking Chris that to diversify I've been thinking about getting another
Platforms and kick and shit. I used to do that more, but lately I've been on rumble only
But I've been thinking it's probably a good idea to
No one needs time
Yeah, I mean like I
I'm getting to the point where I just come on here like to like bullshit and then fucking
Get my hours done. I don't have time either. I got to work man. I gotta get money
These lights they don't they don't turn themselves on you know what I mean
That's true, that's good you're doing your shit
We're all very proud of you Chris
No, I wish it wasn't I wish it wasn't like this man
I wish that was society. I wish we weren't all fucking slaves to money. You know what I mean? Because we are
Society's all fucking we got a fucking get money. We got to work. We got to get money a pair of bills
You know, I mean, I wish this is how it is
Communism doesn't work
It just doesn't work. Cheers. Cheers to Chris. Okay. I hope things get better for him soon
Yeah
So it called a beaker
It's a one shot six milliliters
You need to admit it obviously vodka
Are you the same shit? You always drink that fucking ghetto vodka, bro
What are you gonna listen?
Well right now it's it's too late to get liquor in here
What's the last call and then can yc?
In New York City the the bars could sell liquor after midnight, but liquor stores stop selling
alcohol after midnight
That's dope
So there's better than here
So early I think most bars most bars last call
For the most bars in New York City their last call is about 3 a.m
So they could sell in bars they could sell alcohol till 3 a.m.. But then you go try to go to gas station
I don't know if there's like a hard limit, but but um for bars to sell liquor
I think for the most part they'll close it about 3 a.m.. I don't know if there's a hard limit for them
but um as for beer and
Like four locals malt liquors, whatever that sort of shit. It's 24-7. No, there's no time limit
We'll go you can get a four right now. I'm all liquor
Yes, I can
Okay, you want to get you want to join the YTDC or what?
No
We've been over this Chris
We we've been over this Chris. We've been over this I can repeat myself
Always gonna go is gonna catch up you like five dollars buster girl grab a fucking Chris. You're saying like you're asking me to like join
I'm not I
Don't care Chris. I do not eat. We've already done this. I don't care about joining clothes, dude
I don't give a fuck I
Think pie I could probably get a 40 down
I use this
They're fun
Chris how about how about Chris? How about you send yourself $5 so you can get a real internet connection
Is it that bad?
There's it looks like dog shit my negative that ass
Chris your shit is looks like that
Sorry, sorry chat
I
Don't know these people
First K is streaming in 256 by 256
These streaming in one by one aspect ratio 256 by 256 resolution
Yeah
All right
Enjoying myself. It's late here
fireworks
Are you guys gonna be like good if you're on the panel alone?
No, we need you to tell us what to do please continue telling us what to do
I'm not gonna like even fuck with my shit. I'm just gonna let it I'm almost there. Sorry guys. I'm sorry
So this is my cat and he brought me a bunch of baby bunnies
Ghost cruise
Dave hey Dave
You have a cat named Dave. Oh, that's cute used to like that. It was black and white
Hey, so I so guys I was like Kelly Pailo with Kelly Pailo with this dream for 20 minutes and she's not got a porn
Bob, she's not gonna do anything to take this
Look I come back
Rana already did porn bomb round of a ball. She showed us she showed us her bauhole
She's porn bomb
Chris
Okay, I mean taking back my round of balls
I don't see the chat. I don't
I don't see the chat. I saw
Okay
Yeah, I don't think we've ever actually officially met
How do you know where I'm I'm asking you I'm from Canada. No
I'm from Canada
You are you you are you?
Well, no, I was born in the States. I was born in the States, but yeah, where do you live now?
What's your address?
No, I don't know your house is a big big country the big country goes all we know is you're going with ghosts
Hey, we look we're in Canada looking for you won't find it will kind of very that's not my name
My name is crucible goes okay, so I can't let you knew that's not my name
Like a year down you made a drawing of me. Oh
No
Yo, this is the type of stream. This is the type of stream that Chris K will stay on for three hours
And then this nigga doesn't want to play GTA. Hey, I could you know, this is the type of stream that that that
Oh, no, he left. I was gonna make a
Interesting thing that like you we can have an eight-hour stream and I guarantee that blog gonna stay on the whole eight hours
That dude knows that he even has headphones like underneath it like he always like wears a blog
Yeah, I'm not trying to disrespect. That wasn't an argument. I'm just saying what you know
My boy over here Chris always doesn't have on I mean
I mean sometimes he puts it back
Oh
Look what you did
Summer thank you
I would have dated him if I
You can roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll it roll
Come on. I can't deal with you before actually if you I don't know you don't probably don't remember
Mr. Crowbar
Oh, yeah
There you go. Oh, yeah
Thank you for that
You know, that's I know you like me psyche because you added the dumb dumb in there
You didn't have the dumb dumb. I'd be insulted by that, you know, but
I don't know got he got he got he got it. Give me keep on giving. He's fine. He's fine
We'll laugh at them forever
That fucking drawing is a gift that keeps on given
It says dumb dumb on it. Hey Chris. So
It's a very gay experience yet it when you were in jail. I don't hear about it. So it's funny. You're a boy gay
Did you or no?
I didn't I didn't have any
Okay, guy guy guy this guy is a hundred percent straight
He never had a guy make him a Oreo cookie cake. He never had it
He never had
Gaming and like touching each other he did punch that one dude in the face and Joe so you didn't
I did a peckerwood
He did not care about my treasure. He did not care. You know, I was like, uh, I wasn't, I mean, you're saying you were in, you probably, because you went, you went in there saying you were gay, so you probably could put in a gay set.
No, I didn't. I didn't say things. So if you went to prison and then you're, so you're selling is for three diamonds. What happens the first night?
That's impossible.
by the way
happened once there was a
Not going Chris. I thought you're done. Go ahead, brother
There was a time when I was a man worker and I fucking used to have to mop like like all the units in the middle of the night graveyard and
There was the you know female unit. There's gay units. There's fucking pedophile units
There's you know, all these units fucking protect because you know shit
But I was in the Sally port I was just about I was just about to get out like like five days
I was like gonna get out and fucking cuz I was a man worker
I had to fucking mop the Sally port in the fucking female unit, dude
And like I was just like sitting there like you know because you'll get you'll get fucking written up
Like you get 10 days at it. Cheers. You fucking get caught fucking tried to like flirt with fucking the females
In fucking jail and shit you got a fucking automatically face the wall and fucking let them walk by it not even look at him
If you don't it's a write-up. It's like ten days out of your sins, right?
So how many guys who you hook up with when you're arrested?
I was a assistant wood rep dude
I was assistant wood rep like when a when fucking somebody came into our unit our fucking unit
You know like in a middle of the night like 3 a.m. Was like dude the door be like
I'd have to wake up look and see if it was a white guy in Mexican or whatever
Now what he was talking about Chris. He didn't articulate his point very well
Well, would you like me to articulate your point for you like what would happen
Hey Chris, what he meant was, is flirty diamond, do you know who flirty diamond, do you even
know who that is?
It's a man.
And then like what would happen, what would happen if a man got lied and they identified
they didn't go on a special segment but they got to go to women's prison, what would happen?
And it did happen one time before, you know what would happen.
They fucking would happen, you know, and it did happen
Yeah, they said right like if you sat there and say you're afraid or if you sat there and say you're gay
Usually when you're afraid they just make you go to a different one. They don't like really separate you
But yeah, I understand that but that's what he was asking though. He's like cuz she's a
Can I say the word she's a t-word or he's a t-word whatever you want to call it?
I don't know. I'm trying to be respectful here trying to be respectful
What would happen some man went to a women's prison what would happen?
That's what he was asking
It doesn't really happen. They fucking they they say put yeah, but what he was saying what if what would happen?
Like yeah, we all know the answer. Yeah, we all know the answer
That was this doesn't but I want to say hey pie. Are you really tired, but hi. I want you to do Chris
as a cool guy
I was gonna say pie pie
I just want to say I'm sorry, you know, I'm a fool. Hi, I'm a foolish person. I do things wrong. I'm not
Hi, it's okay. Not to be perfect brother. Hi. I'm not perfect. Hi. Can you forgive me?
Okay, whoa, why do you have to see this stuff on stream? You can't like...
Oh, no, I want to say it to you personally, but I'm okay. I just, right now I'm feeling my, I'm feeling my heart and soul.
Hi, you know I love you and I'm sorry. I just want to say I'm sorry. I want to say it publicly, so it's like
She wants it all straight. It's not you though, brother. Okay
I'm not now, but like tomorrow. No, no, no, I know I mean Android. I do mean if I was stupid
I'm feeling pie right now. It's not since here when you do it on screen, bro, but tomorrow, okay when you're sober. Yeah
Okay, I'll do this tomorrow. I'll say tomorrow.
Why? Why? I'll say I'm sorry.
You don't have to. No, that's okay.
No, because I miss you.
I miss you. I miss you.
I miss you, like, I miss you, like,
not thinking that, like,
or thinking that...
Have you guys seen that movie?
The Temple Grandin movie?
No, we're all apologizing right now.
No, you guys...
Say what say say we're happy apologize. I'd like to say. I'm sorry. Yeah. Yes, you see can we guys all have a hug
Yeah, even if you guys even we hate each other
Yeah
Girls there you're mad, but you're mad
She made an argument though like you hi
Yeah, you're gonna have
Okay
but she said she was here but there's something that can help though hi you're mad you're here right now
you're working on her bro when you apologize on stream that's good but it has to be off stream
brother that's what she really feels it okay hey goes goes let her talk guys let her talk
hi you're you just want to be you just want to be on stream now like that's not i don't i like that
Because you just wanted to like cast everything is just well I'm like, you know, I don't know how I don't know how long I'm gonna be on this earth
Okay, I might be over a very short time and I want to document the whole time in here
You guys can see hi Jeff this guy look at this guy. He's a fucking streamer
Hey, what's up journey shore
Are you being all right? Are you getting science on my chat? What are you? Oh my god. Oh my god
Okay, oh my god
My god, what's taking it? What's that? What is that like little thing peeking peeking out of your little pocket? Okay? Oh, come on
Siamese
Yes guys
Guys, this is the show to make up business. Oh, look at this guy
Yeah, I make it at least the whites in the Mexican through this cat
We're friends forever. We're friends. Yeah. Oh my god. Yeah
Yeah, the next guy's good. Nice gives away. It's finally make out. I love Mexico's away
Hey, 300 what up? Oh, you know what? So like you kind of move me. I would like can I can I take the time to apologize?
You guys don't mind. Yes. Yes. Apologies. Yeah, I like to take this time to apologize to absolutely nobody
Oh, Chris does what he wants. Yo, Chris
Yo, Chris me and how can I mean how come we're gonna get on GT air you're gonna get
Off buster you first kiss I can't
I said you almost as if you're talking out of the cat. Look out. Look at this kitty cat buddy.
I'm not only a guy, but one good looking cat. I'll tell you.
Fuck you. Come from a guy who doesn't even come out. Take off.
Oh, oh, look at you. You throw gang signs up with your right hand, but on the left hand you make balloon animals.
He's doing it. What's the one night? What? What night?
That's how you jerk me off one time and his wife in the mind she was I gave her like 20 bucks
Yeah
Never mind, it was a joke. There's a joke. Oh, look at the cat. Hey, God, I can't get up here. God. Do you have a red pie?
Oh, my God. Did you have
Well, I know you look you know what? I don't mean to be disrespectful. You look sweaty though. I know it's hot with that hat
Do you have a hat on
I'll tell you what I wear this hot all weather. I'll be I'll be butt naked. I'll be butt naked not wearing nothing
I will be butt naked and I will still have the hat on yes, sir
I was gonna rob the chat. Where'd you have it stop it? It's not funny. What's your gang called mr. Good or miss gendered
Oh
I'm a black guy, and I hate white people
You're a gangsta y'all. You don't know where you fall man or female
It's so stupid slow like
Brandy tastes like orange juice
Oh
Pretty cool in a mask
Yeah, I like it. Oh you go for a second one. My brother is oh
Here you are
flirty
Love you
Your wife is there. Is your wife there? Yeah
Hey
Okay, I know that's hot with that mask on brother
Well, why why?
What are you drinking? Are you drinking beer?
With with brandy brand Randy. Okay. I'm gonna do it
We're it was your wife looking looking at you with a special look on her face
And she's looking at me with a shame like she's like why the fuck did I do this like I knew better?
She's looking at you like I made a mistake in the world
Okay, DJ Khali
Oh, we were guest guys, we were guest hello
Hello, it's Reggie Deman, Reggie Deman is here.
Hello, I'm not Reggie Deman, you're paranoid, not up.
I thought that up, oh no.
Oh my god, I'm a confused one.
Crash out Deman.
Are you paranoid?
You are, what, I'm not Reggie Deman.
Reggie Deman's a set out loser that talks like he's a big man.
Sounds like you're a fucking wanker, a bloody fucking wanker.
So, Raging Deepman, he talks like he's a big guy, he doesn't know anything about anything.
Oh, that's the champion.
What's up? Your mother's
What are you talking about? Where's
where's that signal? Where's
that signal? That's me. That's
me. That's me. That's me.
That's me. That's me. That's
me. That's me. That's me. That's
me. That's me. That's me.
That's me. That's me. That's
me. That's me. That's me. That's
me. That's me. That's me.
What is it? What is it? What is that? What are you doing?
Look at her. Look at her. She's loving it.
I knew you.
It's nice to meet you, Pie.
It's God. It's God.
That's right. It's God.
I'm a sensitive you in a pink T-shirt.
You can borrow if you want.
You got my range. Look at that f***ing kitchen face. Look at it baby. Come on. You got your
You don't get it. If you turn it around, you'll see the toilet in here.
Do you want to see it? Do you want to see it?
Hey, there's our Zesty, there's our Zesty Warrior.
Oh, this guy, he's getting ready to rape his wife.
What the f**k are you doing with your monster?
No, he's getting ready to beat his wife.
He's going to drink a monster and he's going to hit her.
Yo, that's not allowed. That's not allowed on YouTube.
Oh, Isaiah's there too in the dark.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. I'm allowed on. Thank God.